You want to join the training team?
I'm afraid it won't be that easy.
Please, help me figure something out.
I'll do anything.
There actually is one way.
But...
Please, just tell me.
The training team...
currently has an opening for a Logistics Support Team Leader.
I'll do it.
Don't agree so quickly.
Although the Logistics Support Team Leader is part of the team,
you won't participate in the training itself.
You'll only be responsible for logistics.
A graduate student like you...
is willing to do that?
I am.
There is no high or low in military work.
Every position has its indispensable function.
Even pouring tea, sweeping, or serving meals,
someone has to do it, right?
Although it's far from my goal,
as long as I get into the training team,
what I learn is up to me.
Is that really what you think?
It really is.
Good.
That's the Guo Zijian I want to see.
I'll report this to the superiors.
But as for the outcome,
you need to prepare for both possibilities.
I still need to prepare for both outcomes?
I've heard everything.
The training is here in our Training Unit.
It's close by and convenient for me.
Your situation is different, Guo Zijian.
After we finish our review,
we still have to report to the Group Army.
They have to approve it.
I don't care. I know you have a way.
Thank you in advance, sir.
All right, you can go back.
Yes, sir.
Commissar.
Hurry up.
I know.
Reporting.
Come in.
Sir, about Guo Zijian...
Could we make an exception?
How can we make an exception?
He is at the center of public opinion.
You tell me how to make an exception.
Have a seat.
Let's skip what happened before.
He's been removed as battalion commander.
But think back on it.
At the Training Unit,
how beautifully he fought Long Yuanshan.
Also,
the special ops squad he led himself
in the graduation competition,
won the Group Army championship.
By all accounts, during the training,
we should give him a position.
So you're saying
his stylish flying kick
can just be ignored?
Then what should we do?
We can make it happen.
Ling Jun,
if Guo Zijian can only rely on our support
to make progress,
then such progress is worthless,
and it's unfair to the others.
But Sir,
when we poached him in the first place,
wasn't it for today's training?
Logically speaking, this move,
was flawless from layout to execution.
But now there's a problem with the piece.
He acts on his own
and always tries to break the rules.
Tell me, what should I do?
Then,
are we really keeping Guo Zijian out?
Ling Jun.
Kang Baoping, 396th Brigade Commissar,
is an old hand at managing personnel.
Yet you never give him credit.
Old Kang...
what brilliant move did he make?
Here's the training roster just submitted.
Take a good look at it.
Logistics Support Team Leader
Old Kang...
is truly a seasoned political officer.
I have to hand it to him.
Logistics Support Team Leader?
How is that possible?
Why wouldn't it be?
The list has already been submitted.
As for Guo Zijian,
I can sum him up simply:
He had it coming.
Last drill, Guo Zijian and a dozen men
almost captured Long Yuanshan.
I was hoping that during this training,
I could go head-to-head with him.
Why bother doing that?
Isn't it nice to have one less rival?
A rival is a rival.
Facing off directly makes it meaningful.
Otherwise, it's a hollow victory.
Short sword or long sword,
a good sword wins tough battles.
The process doesn't matter.
Right, speaking of the last drill,
it just reminded me of something.
That matter wasn't so simple.
I've been looking into it for a while.
And now I finally have some clues.
This guy, Guo Zijian,
plays dirty.
What do you mean?
Never mind. You'll find out soon enough.
Comrades,
The New-Type Combat Forces core training
is assigned to our Group Army
as an exploratory and innovative
important mission by the Theater Command.
Every single one of you sitting here today
can feel proud of yourselves,
and feel honored,
because you represent this era's
crucial frontier in Army development.
What are New-Type Combat Forces?
In my view, they represent
a new starting point,
a generation point,
an elevation point, and a breakthrough.
Of course, there is one more,
which is a new integration point.
Comrades,
how will future land battles be fought?
Have you thought about it?
This is a practical subject,
as well as an exploratory one.
The Chinese Army,
if it wants to uphold its historical responsibility,
cannot stick to the old ways.
It must build upon its glorious history
and forge more combat power for the future.
Look at you. What's so funny?
Getting assigned to do logistics with me.
Don't you feel wronged?
Well, maybe a little bit.
But...
what matters most...
is that I still get to work with you.
See? What did I tell you?
1st Battalion will be yours eventually.
Stop talking nonsense.
How is it nonsense?
Look, all these signs show
that you've already stepped onto
the golden path back to the 1st Battalion.
According to my analysis,
as long as you are here, Commander,
even if we're in the mess squad,
we still have chances to earn merits.
Right?
You're pretty confident.
Of course.
I'm mainly confident in you.
Trust my judgment.
Just wait and see.
This time,
the training is on a tight schedule,
so a lot of basic preparations
can't be done perfectly in one go.
Regarding this,
I ask for your understanding.
Our comrades in charge of logistics
are also working very hard.
They don't even have the time
to attend our mobilization meeting.
What are they busy with?
Transporting equipment for everyone.
After the meeting ends,
everyone, on a squad basis,
can go and collect your gear.
I've been thinking about this,
and the leaders really have their ways.
Though you aren't in the training,
you're the Logistics Support Team Leader.
In short,
it accounts for that flying kick of yours,
and keeps you from missing out.
It's basically a roundabout approach.
Killing two birds with one stone, right?
What roundabout approach?
Stop saying things like that.
Understood, understood.
I'll keep a low profile.
I'm telling you,
The Army Commander and I at the Group Army
have already made a military pledge.
The two of you, one chief and one deputy,
must ensure all tasks are carried out.
Yes, sir!
Please rest assured, Chief.
We will do our absolute best.
Comrade Jian'an,
Here!
You are an expert in military theory
and a specialist in troop management.
You must utilize your strengths.
Yes, sir!
I will not let you down, sir.
On the modern battlefield,
New-Type Combat Forces frequently emerge.
Only by speeding up our pace
can we avoid being left behind.
Yes, sir!
Let's go.
Salute.
Zeng Muhan.
Here!
Next.
Show me your officer ID and training pass.
The name matches,
but you don't look like the photo.
Sir!
Normally,
a photo is just a two-dimensional display,
while a real person is three-dimensional.
All right, all right.
Here.
Go on,
go get your things.
Recon platoon equipment.
Squad Leader Yang, Special Ops Team?
I'm Hong Xiafei.
Next.
Yang Mao...
Yang Maolin.
So you're Yang Maolin.
That's me.
You look pretty ordinary.
Next.
Squad Leader Hong.
Squad Leader Hong is an old friend.
No need to check.
You people from the training base
are also joining the training this time.
Why wouldn't we be?
This is a Theater Command Army pilot,
not some private game of house.
Are you trying to exclude people?
What are you talking about?
How could we?
Squad Leader Hong, what do you need?
Electronic warfare.
Electronic warfare?
Why switch to electronic warfare?
Company Commander Li.
Are you running a background check on me?
Though I usually work as an adjudicator,
my primary specialty
is communications and electronic warfare.
Besides,
do I need your approval for everything?
No, you don't.
I'm just...
a bit confused.
Here, Squad Leader Hong.
Go get it over there.
Electronic warfare equipment.
Come on, next.
These devices are highly sophisticated.
Make sure to handle them with care.
Yes, sir.
Guo...
Battalion Commander Guo.
Squad Leader Hong.
Why are you here?
This is the 396th Brigade Training Unit.
I'm an instructor for the Training Unit.
If I'm not here, where else would I be?
Right, right, right.
Hold that equipment securely.
Handle it with care.
Battalion Commander Guo, I'll get going.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Battalion Commander Guo.
Commander.
Everything meets its match.
You had quite the presence just now.
Squad Leader Hong was like,
"Battalion Commander Guo,
goodbye."
Quit messing around.
Register them quickly, people are waiting.
Next!
Right.
Next.
Staff Officer Liang,
guess who I saw.
Guo Zijian.
How did you know?
It's written all over your face.
Is it that obvious?
But did you know?
He's issuing gear in Logistics Support.
Isn't that a huge waste of his talents?
As long as he's in the training team,
regardless of his position,
having a place means he has a chance.
Staff Officer Liang.
Staff Officer Liang!
Are you busy?
If you're not,
I have something to ask you.
Section Chief Liu, no need to be formal.
Go ahead.
It's about the end of the last drill.
When Guo Zijian
led Yang Maolin's decapitation strike.
In the end,
were you two the only ones at the scene?
Yes. Is there a problem?
Well, someone reported
Guo Zijian deliberately stalled for time,
letting Long Yuanshan off the hook.
I don't know if that's true,
so I wanted to ask you about it.
Deliberately stalled for time?
Why would anyone think that?
Have they lost their minds?
As for such claims,
it's better to ask the person involved.
As adjudicators,
we only observe and record the facts.
As for all sorts of speculations or
psychological intentions,
we have no way to judge them.
That makes sense.
Alright.
With an answer like that,
thank you very much.
I'll get back to work.
Staff Officer Liang!
Section Chief Liu is always so paranoid.
Baffling.
Hurry up, stop dawdling!
The soldiers are waiting to eat.
Solid Logistics Support Team Leader work.
Of course.
You own whatever you're doing.
You pitch whatever you're selling.
Then let me ask you,
if someone acts one way to your face
and another way behind your back,
how do you pitch
something like that?
What do you mean?
I don't follow.
Bad memory?
Forgot what you just did?
I've done a lot of things.
Unloaded and issued gear this morning.
And there's a pile of vegetables up there.
If you're so free,
want to lend a hand?
Don't play games with me.
What's done in the dark comes to light.
Let me ask you,
during the last exercise,
did you let Long Yuanshan off on purpose?
I'm not afraid to tell you,
I found the evidence.
Is that so?
Then you've earned a merit.
Go report to the superiors now.
Guo Zijian,
you can't expect
to cover this up.
The higher-ups aren't fools.
You think running to the training team
to be the Logistics Support Team Leader
means you can get away with it?
The rice pot incident isn't over yet.
Add this to the list,
you'll be punished for both.
You'll be in for
a world of trouble.
Liu Wangyuan.
I can't be bothered with people like you.
If this were two years ago,
do you know what I'd do to you?
What are you going to do?
You want to hit me?
You're nothing.
Speed it up!
Don't delay Section Chief Liu's meal.
Yes, sir!
You're the one who's nothing!
What are you looking at?
Get to work!
Comrade.
Don't waste food.
I'm talking to you.
Squad Leader Wu wants a word with you.
About what?
Tonight at 2100.
At the PT field.
He'll be waiting.
Yang Maolin.
Meet me at the gate after you eat.
Yes, sir.
Wangyuan,
you're Chief of the Operations and Training Section.
This event may be a Group Army project,
but
the team leader is the Operations Director.
You cannot slack off.
Of course. It's my duty, after all.
Tonight,
inspect the training grounds thoroughly.
See if anything needs to be improved.
The Group Army is training here.
We must ensure solid logistics support.
Then I'm doing Guo Zijian's job.
He's the Logistics Support Team Leader.
Don't be so petty.
It's all part of our job.
Don't forget.
Alright.
Why is Lin Yihu looking for you?
He said Squad Leader Wu sent a message.
To meet him at the PT field at 9 PM.
And you believe that?
Are you stupid?
He's looking for trouble.
Can't you see that?
Why would he want to cause me trouble?
Are you dense?
Because of the Squad Leader Wu incident.
Look at his attitude toward you.
Can't you see it?
Don't you have a training class tonight?
I was just worrying about that.
You go to your training.
I'll go in your place.
You will?
What?
You think I can't handle these punks?
Go on.
Yes.
Remember this later, guys.
We can't actually beat Yang Maolin up.
We're just teaching him a lesson. Hear me?
Don't worry.
Alright, alright, alright.
Here he comes, here he comes.
Who knows what Captain Wang is thinking.
Pitch black, and no light set up.
Who is it?
These little brats.
I swear I'll catch you!
I'll try to hold the fort initially.
But once the training gets on track,
I'll need you to step up, Old Suo.
Of course.
Operations is the Group Army's largest.
I know you're busy.
If anything comes up,
just leave it to me.
Right now is the training prep phase.
I have plenty of time.
Then thanks for your support.
Chief.
This... This Guo Zijian.
He's completely out of line!
Crap, crap.
We were just meant to scare Yang Maolin,
but we bagged Scheming Liu instead.
Tell me,
if he reports us for officer assault,
what are we gonna do?
Don't talk nonsense.
That wasn't an assault.
It was a prank at most.
You know how much he values his pride.
He won't just swallow this.
Tell me,
what should we do?
About what happened today,
everyone keep your mouths shut tight.
If anyone leaks a word,
all four of us will go down together.
We'll all get kicked out and sent packing.
If word gets out about this,
it'd be too humiliating.
We must keep this to ourselves.
He doesn't know it was us anyway,
right?
Right.
How about
we just wash up and go to sleep?
No, it's too early.
Then what should we do?
Let's go.
Let's practice boxing by headquarters.
It's the brightest there.
We need to make sure they see us.
Right, right, right.
Let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Capture drills, combat stance!
Kill!
Movement one!
Movement two!
Kill!
Where are they?
Over here.
Movement three!
Kill!
Movement four!
The training ground?
Yes.
Why are they heading to the training ground?
It's fine, don't panic.
They weren't asking us.
Keep practicing.
Okay.
These brats...
They can't even pick a fight on time.
Where?
Just up ahead.
Right around these sandbags.
And then I got pushed into this pit.
This one.
Who's there?
It's me, Guo Zijian.
Guo Zijian?
It's so late,
what are you doing?
Director.
What are you doing here?
What are we doing here?
You have the nerve to ask?
Was that you just now, Guo Zijian?
I bet you didn't expect
that I'd come right back, did you?
Come right back?
Lost your mind, Section Chief Liu?
Stop interrupting! I'm asking you,
what are you doing here this late?
Sir!
I'm here to resolve an internal conflict.
Sirs, listen to him!
Is this how you solve internal conflicts?
I mean, Guo Zijian,
this is an egregious offense!
This is a very serious problem.
Alright.
Let's not discuss this here.
Back to the office. We'll talk there.
Come, come here.
Kill!
Movement one!
Movement two!
Kill!
What's wrong? You look half-dead.
Movement three!
Kill!
Movement four!
You soldiers over there,
what are you doing so late?
Sir!
It's bright here,
so we're practicing a bit.
Alright.
Get some rest early.
Yes, sir.
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
I think you really need to practice.
Oh no, oh no.
This has blown up.
They even called our battalion commander in.
Stop talking nonsense.
Right now, there's no evidence,
so no one can do anything to us.
Besides,
the commanders just saw us.
They'd never suspect us.
Yeah.
No evidence, no crime.
As long as they don't have proof,
they can't catch us.
That's right.
Come on, let's keep practicing, guys.
Sirs,
you have to get justice for me.
Not only did he put a sack over me,
he put sand inside it.
Look at how red my eyes are.
I'm almost blind!
Section Chief Liu,
you need proof for your claims.
That sack covered your whole head,
so how could you see it was me?
Do you have X-ray vision?
Stop being so stubborn!
You know exactly what you did.
Stop playing dumb!
That's right.
Exactly.
That stinky sweat smell on him,
I could smell it even blindfolded!
So not only do you have X-ray vision,
you also have the skills of an army dog.
You!
Sir!
He just called me a dog!
Enough about the dog.
Let's talk about the human matters.
Then how do you explain the dirt on your boots?
The dirt on my boots
is because I saw
the training ground's sandbag wall fell,
so I stacked it back up.
Excuses!
Guo Zijian,
tell the truth.
Did you assault Chief Liu or not?
Sir, I did not.
The evidence is solid.
And you still refuse to admit it?
Director.
What's my reputation in the 396th Brigade?
If you don't know,
you can ask around.
For years, from superiors to subordinates,
I haven't had a conflict with anyone.
Moreover, everyone treats me
with respect and like a brother.
There's no one who doesn't like me.
How come before,
our brigade never had such incidents?
But the moment Guo Zijian arrives,
such a vicious incident occurs?
Why?
It's because he's never liked me.
He has a problem with me.
Guo Zijian,
if you have a problem with me, say it to my face.
I, Liu Wangyuan,
am not someone who can't take criticism.
If you really want to get physical,
we can have a face-to-face match.
It's anyone's guess who'd win.
You're laughing?
Commander, look at his attitude.
Chief Liu,
you've got it backwards.
You're the one with a problem with me.
Always staying on my case.
I admit I don't really like you.
But I'm not stupid enough
to ambush you in the dark.
You hear that?
He admitted he doesn't like me!
Right, you aren't stupid.
You're so sneaky.
Last exercise, you let Long Yuanshan off.
Wasn't that just quid pro quo
to get into the 404th Brigade?
But think about it,
with your habit of kicking over pots,
would they even want you?
Only our brigade's leaders are so lenient.
Enough.
You're pretty good at sowing discord too.
That's a separate matter.
Kicking the pot and hitting you
are two completely unrelated things.
Besides,
I never wanted to join the 404th Brigade.
You know very well if you thought about it.
But then again,
if you can lose your temper and kick someone's pot,
couldn't you snap and ambush me?
Just stick to the facts.
Why bring up unrelated things?
They're practically the same thing!
Alright, that's enough.
Guo Zijian.
You are a soldier.
A veteran.
A battalion commander now.
Don't you know military regulations?
What the consequences of this are,
don't you understand?
No, I really didn't hit him.
Besides,
how would I know he'd go to the training ground?
I knew you'd use that excuse.
Today at noon, outside the cafeteria,
when Deputy Brigade Commander Suo told me
to inspect the training ground tonight...
Where were you?
Weren't you right there?
Did you think I didn't see you?
But I never imagined,
Guo Zijian,
that you hated me this much.
You couldn't hold back for a second, could you?
You just threatened me this morning,
and came after me tonight.
Why on earth would you do that?
Commanders,
from the moment I was hit until now,
I've been thinking about this too.
Really.
But after thinking it over,
I could only come up with one possibility.
He's afraid I'll expose him.
Guo Zijian!
You have a guilty conscience!
If you insist on framing me, I have nothing to say.
Having nothing to say isn't an option.
You have to speak up.
Reporting to Deputy Brigade Commander Suo.
First of all,
I never threatened Section Chief Liu.
Even if we had a verbal conflict,
it doesn't mean I had to hit him.
There's no direct connection between the two.
Second,
this morning at the cafeteria,
when assigning Section Chief Liu the task,
I was indeed present.
But I didn't hear
what you were talking about.
And about this dirt...
I just explained it.
The reason I went to the training ground was because...
Because of what?
I'm talking to you.
Squad Leader Wu has something to say to you.
What did Lin Yihu want with you?
He said Squad Leader Wu asked him to pass a message,
to meet him at the PT field at 9 PM.
Are you stupid?
He's looking for trouble.
Can't you see that?
What are those soldiers
doing so late at night?
Reporting to the Commander,
it's bright over here,
so we're training here for a bit.
Keep lying.
Just keep making things up.
Just like Section Chief Liu,
I was worried, so I went to take a look.
Guo Zijian,
if you really didn't hit him,
do you have any suspects?
Who do you think hit him?
I don't know that.
Regarding Section Chief Liu getting beaten,
I also feel very sorry.
But relying on this baseless
so-called evidence
to slander me as the culprit...
I refuse to accept it.
This isn't enough evidence?
And you still have the nerve to argue!
Section Chief Liu, Section Chief Liu!
Calm down first.
The organization will investigate this.
Old Suo,
why don't you take Section Chief Liu
to the clinic for a checkup first?
Guo Zijian.
In short, this incident
is extremely serious.
I'm giving you one night
to think it over carefully.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I expect you to give me,
the training unit,
and the brigade party committee
a clear and definitive answer.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Commander Suo, are we letting this go?
Take the sack with you.
Guo Zijian
What am I supposed to say to you?
I hoped as Logistics Support Team Leader
to seize the opportunity and perform well.
Is this how you perform?
Director, I really didn't hit him.
But all the evidence points to you now.
Section Chief Liu insists you did it.
How do you explain that?
The incident with the pot isn't even over yet,
and now you've caused this mess.
What are you trying to do?
Will you only rest when you're stripped of your uniform?
No, what he's saying is ridiculous.
Would I even stoop to hitting him?
Besides,
I'm not the only one who dislikes him.
All right then.
You say you didn't hit him.
Then find out who did.
Even if there are personal grudges,
they should be settled honorably.
Stabbing someone in the back,
what kind of comrade does that?
What is a comrade?
Who takes a bullet for you in battle.
A unit that can win battles
must have absolute trust
and absolute unity.
What happened tonight is unacceptable.
Yes, sir.
I'll investigate immediately
and give you an answer as soon as possible.
First movement.
Kill!
The battalion commander is here.
Cut the chatter. Second movement.
Kill!
He's here. He's here. He's here.
Third movement.
Kill!
Fourth movement.
Fall in!
Battalion Commander.
Need us to run any errands?
Deputy Commander Suo and Director Xu asked for you.
You're still up this late?
Tonight, Liu Wangyuan...
...got beaten up on the training ground.
The commanders asked me about the situation.
Battalion Commander.
Section Chief Liu...
...isn't exactly popular anyway.
Who knows who he offended.
Don't you think?
Where were you guys around 9:00 PM?
We...
...were right here sparring.
We didn't go anywhere.
Go back and get some rest.
Yes, sir.
Do you think
they spotted us?
You idiot.
If they had, would we still stand here?
Don't worry.
As long as we keep our mouths shut,
nobody can do anything to us.
I regret it so much right now.
I mean,
how could we be so unlucky?
We could have hit anyone else,
but it just had to be Petty Liu.
Cut the crap.
Did you hit him or not?
I was the one who hit Liu Wangyuan.
I'm willing to accept disciplinary action.
Then why didn't you admit it last night?
Because Liu Wangyuan had no solid evidence
to prove that I did it.
So I took my chances,
thinking I could escape punishment.
Think carefully before you speak.
Let me ask you,
did you already find out who did it?
No.
It was me.
Guo Zijian,
do you know,
once this is confirmed,
what consequences you will face?
Whatever the consequences are,
I accept them.
I really didn't expect
you would sink this low.
Chief Xu,
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo,
I am sorry.
I let you down.
This morning,
after a night of consideration, Guo Zijian
officially admitted to me
and Director Xu
that the sack incident
was his doing alone.
No, no, no.
No matter how you look at it,
I don't believe he did it.
True.
Guo Zijian can be a bit childish,
and his words and actions aren't always mature.
Sometimes he even acts a bit extreme.
But based on what I know of him,
he is honorable and aboveboard.
These dirty tricks of messing with people,
he simply wouldn't stoop to them.
That's because he wasn't pushed to the edge.
According to Liu Wangyuan,
he obtained video evidence of Guo Zijian
purposely stalling the decapitation strike.
Evidence?
And yesterday morning,
he confronted him directly.
So Guo Zijian panicked,
and even threatened to deal with him.
And look,
as soon as night fell,
the incident happened.
Video of delaying the decapitation strike?
Is the evidence conclusive?
It's clear as day.
The facts are there.
How could there be such a coincidence?
Just one second off.
A coincidence doesn't mean it's impossible.
Commissar.
I know.
Emotionally speaking,
you don't want to believe this.
I didn't believe it at first either.
But now I do.
This kid
most likely held back during the drill.
Do you know why?
We removed him as battalion commander.
He held a grudge and took it to heart.
To be honest,
through this drill,
I admit
he is indeed capable.
He fought a beautiful battle.
But you can't let personal emotions
override collective honor.
Besides,
in just a few days,
look how many things happened.
The pot-kicking incident,
the decapitation strike incident,
and the sack incident.
Every single one of these
has become an unexplained mystery.
This kind of person
is absolutely not a qualified commander.
How do you expect me to trust him?
Yes.
Loyalty,
first and foremost, requires
overcoming personal emotions and motives.
He couldn't overcome them.
Old Suo,
this incident
will have a huge impact on Guo Zijian.
I'll say it again.
I still don't think he'd be so irrational.
He was irrational.
Let's investigate further.
What's there to investigate now?
He admitted it himself.
Witnesses, physical evidence,
the culprit's confession...
What culprit's confession?
In the civilian world, he'd be arrested already.
You're exaggerating.
Commissar
I know
you value talent.
But Guo Zijian...
He smashed someone else's pot,
we still put him on the Logistics Support Team.
But does he know how to cherish it?
Is he worthy of his uniform?
Besides,
Liu Wangyuan is very emotionally unstable right now.
He repeatedly reiterated to me
that if the brigade party committee
doesn't handle this matter impartially,
he'll report it up the chain of command,
until justice is served.
Old Suo,
Liu Wangyuan usually listens to you.
You can't let him cause more trouble.
Don't worry about that.
I'll talk to him.
All right.
Convene a party committee meeting.
To discuss how to deal with Guo Zijian.
Staff Officer Liang,
I need to report something.
Go ahead.
Someone copied a segment of
the drill inspection video from days ago.
So what?
Isn't it good to review after a drill?
Is there a problem?
A huge problem.
The person who copied the video is Liu Wangyuan.
He only copied Guo Zijian and Yang Maolin
carrying out the decapitation strike.
Why
copy this part?
Is there a problem with this part?
Did you forget?
This part caused the most controversy
in the entire exercise.
Moreover,
many people say
Guo Zijian purposely let Long Yuanshan go.
Section Chief Liu has also been investigating this.
He's certain Guo Zijian hit him,
probably because of this.
No way.
Guo Zijian couldn't have hit anyone.
It was so hard for him to get into the training team.
He wouldn't be that irrational.
I think so too.
But who knows what he's thinking?
He actually admitted it.
Then it must be because he knows who it is,
and wants to protect them.
Seeing how he almost got discharged
because of the Wu Dongsheng incident,
you can tell what kind of personality he has.
He's typically protective of his own.
Is Liu Wangyuan badly hurt?
Badly hurt?
The clinic said he wasn't even scratched.
However,
if he makes an issue of the video,
then Guo Zijian is in real trouble.
Wouldn't we both become accomplices?
What kind of luck does Guo Zijian have?
Why is he so unlucky?
Maybe we can do something.